<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Joseph Lee | A designer living in Seattle</title>
    <link>http://josephrlee.com</link>
    <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2019 00:17:37 -0700</pubDate>
    
    <item>
      <title>Seattle Urban Academy</title>
      <link>http://josephrlee.com/home/sua</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2019 21:39:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <author>Joseph Lee</author>
      <guid>http://josephrlee.com/home/sua</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Seattle Urban Academy is a positive, educational community where students overcome risks to graduate and succeed in life. I designed a new site to help SUA attract new students and also acquire new donors.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Witness The Transformation</title>
      <link>http://josephrlee.com/home/witness</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jul 2015 21:10:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <author>Joseph Lee</author>
      <guid>http://josephrlee.com/home/witness</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A new shiny website is nice, but it means nothing if it doesn’t get people engaged. So, to accompany the launch of World Concern’s website, I thought it was important to create a handsome splash site that told a great story. By reading the story of &lt;a href=&quot;http://worldconcern.org/donate/campaigns/chad/&quot; title=&quot;Check out Achta and Yaya’s Story&quot;&gt;Achta and Yaya’s&lt;/a&gt; family, visitors easily see 6 different ways they can make an impact. The call to action at the bottom of the page encourages visitors to explore the website further. This splash site helped generate more traffic to the website and created buzz on social media.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Global Gift Guide</title>
      <link>http://josephrlee.com/home/global-gift-guide</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jun 2015 17:29:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <author>Joseph Lee</author>
      <guid>http://josephrlee.com/home/global-gift-guide</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Every Holiday season, World Concern rolls out the &lt;a href=&quot;https://globalgiftguide.org&quot; title=&quot;Visit the Global Gift Guide&quot;&gt;Global Gift Guide&lt;/a&gt;, it&amp;rsquo;s a gift catalog that changes lives. This past holiday season, we moved platforms on to Shopify, and we built a custom card feature. I was responsible for the design and front-end development of the site.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Also, as a part of our &lt;a href=&quot;https://globalgiftguide.org/givingtuesday&quot; title=&quot;View the Campaign&quot;&gt;Giving Tuesday campaign&lt;/a&gt;, I created a character named Totes Ma Goates, a charming goat that encouraged generous giving. We rolled out a whole marketing campaign: he had a jingle, Facebook ads, Tweets, and an email series. Because of this hair-brained idea, Giving Tuesday raised $54,000.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>World Concern</title>
      <link>http://josephrlee.com/home/world-concern</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jun 2015 16:51:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <author>Joseph Lee</author>
      <guid>http://josephrlee.com/home/world-concern</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In 2013 I led the redesign of &lt;a href=&quot;http://worldconcern.org/&quot; title=&quot;Visit the Site&quot;&gt;World Concern&amp;rsquo;s website&lt;/a&gt; with an amazing team. We transformed the previously static website into a beautifully responsive experience, solidifying World Concern’s reputation as a trustworthy nonprofit.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I believe in the power of story-telling through photography, so I made it a priority to showcase World Concern’s rich imagery. By telling the stories of beneficiaries and their changed lives, the redesign increased fundraising dramatically. Since the redesign, I’ve been responsible for maintaining and upgrading the website with each new fundraising campaign.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
