<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Joseph Lee | A designer living in Seattle</title>
    <link>http://josephrlee.com</link>
    <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2019 14:21:02 -0700</pubDate>
    
    <item>
      <title>Remember A Pet</title>
      <link>http://josephrlee.com/home/remember-a-pet</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2019 14:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <author>Joseph Lee</author>
      <guid>http://josephrlee.com/home/remember-a-pet</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Remember a Pet is a personalized pet sympathy card ordering service. Its primary audience is veterinary clinics. I was responsible for the visual design and front end development of the site. I worked with a software engineer and we built the site on top of Shopify. It was launched in March of 2016 and I&amp;rsquo;ve had the opportunity to work on and watch it grow. &lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Seattle Urban Academy</title>
      <link>http://josephrlee.com/home/sua</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2019 21:39:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <author>Joseph Lee</author>
      <guid>http://josephrlee.com/home/sua</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Designed a new website for Seattle Urban Academy to simplify the navigation and improve the user experience. The redesign focused on optimizing the site for two unique audiences: students/parents and donors/volunteers in order to increase school enrollment and acquire new donors. Also integrated a digital volunteer solution that connects with Salesforce. SUA is a positive, educational community where students overcome risks to graduate high school. &lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Witness The Transformation</title>
      <link>http://josephrlee.com/home/witness</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jul 2015 21:10:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <author>Joseph Lee</author>
      <guid>http://josephrlee.com/home/witness</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Designed and developed a robust landing page to increase engagement for World Concern&amp;rsquo;s new website. Users were drawn in through Achta&amp;rsquo;s story as they learned about six different ways her family needed help and what areas World Concern worked in. The call to action at the bottom of the page encourages users to take a specific action by further exploring the website. This landing page generated twice as much traffic over the months it was live on the main site.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Global Gift Guide</title>
      <link>http://josephrlee.com/home/global-gift-guide</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jun 2015 17:29:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <author>Joseph Lee</author>
      <guid>http://josephrlee.com/home/global-gift-guide</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;World Concern&amp;rsquo;s &lt;a href=&quot;https://globalgiftguide.org&quot; title=&quot;Visit the Global Gift Guide&quot;&gt;Global Gift Guide&lt;/a&gt; is an e-commerce website that invites shoppers to help change lives in the world&amp;rsquo;s poorest places by purchasing a practical gift. Last holiday season, I migrated the Global Gift Guide website to Shopify and was responsible for the design and front-end development of the new site.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>World Concern</title>
      <link>http://josephrlee.com/home/world-concern</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jun 2015 16:51:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <author>Joseph Lee</author>
      <guid>http://josephrlee.com/home/world-concern</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In 2013, I led the redesign of &lt;a href=&quot;http://worldconcern.org/&quot; title=&quot;Visit the Site&quot;&gt;World Concern&amp;rsquo;s&lt;/a&gt; website with a small but talented team consisting of a developer and a writer. We transformed the static website into a user-friendly, responsive experience, helping to solidify World Concern&amp;rsquo;s reputation as a trustworthy nonprofit. One of my primary objectives was to use rich imagery to help convey the story of World Concern and its beneficiaries. By telling visually compelling stories of transformation, the redesign helped to increase fundraising revenue by 14% and conversion rates by 123% year over year. Following the redesign, I&amp;rsquo;ve also been responsible for maintaining and upgrading the website for each new fundraising campaign. In 2017, I implemented a new donation platform that integrated with Salesforce. &lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
